<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Los Angeles Music Guide</string>
    <string name="venues">Venues</string>
    <string name="studios">Studios</string>
    <string name="stores">Stores</string>
    <string name="iconic_locations">Iconic Locations</string>

    <string name="studio_one_name">Capitol Studios</string>
    <string name="studio_one_address">1750 Vine St, Los Angeles, CA 90028</string>
    <string name="studio_one_description">Since its completion in 1956, Capitol Studios
        has been a staple of the recording industry. Iconic artists like Frank Sinatra,
        Nat King Cole and The Beach Boys first gave life to its rooms and to this day,
        major icons of popular music continue in their wake.</string>

    <string name="studio_two_name">Conway Studios</string>
    <string name="studio_two_address">5100 Melrose Ave, Hollywood, CA 90038</string>
    <string name="studio_two_description">It started in 1972 as an eight track mastering
        studio, and was later purchased by Buddy and Susan Brundo in 1976. Since then,
        the studio complex has been rebuilt from the ground up by studio designer and
        architect Vincent Van Haaff.</string>

    <string name="studio_three_name">EastWest Studios</string>
    <string name="studio_three_address">6000 Sunset Blvd, Los Angeles, CA 90028</string>
    <string name="studio_three_description">EastWest Studios (formerly known as Western
        Studio, a component of United Western Recorders and later Ocean Way Recording)
        is a recording studio complex located at 6000 West Sunset Boulevard in Hollywood.
        Originally constructed by Bill Putnam in the 1960s, the studios are currently owned
        by sound developer Doug Rogers and managed by Candace Stewart.</string>

    <string name="venue_one_name">The Forum</string>
    <string name="venue_one_address">3900 W Manchester Blvd, Inglewood, CA 90305</string>
    <string name="venue_one_description">The Forum became a landmark in greater Los Angeles,
        largely due to the Lakers\' success and the Hollywood celebrities often seen there.
        It hosted tennis matches, music concerts, boxing matches and U. S. political events.
        The arena is sometimes called the "Los Angeles Forum" or the "L. A. Forum" to distinguish
        it from other places with the name "Forum".</string>

    <string name="venue_two_name">Hollywood Bowl</string>
    <string name="venue_two_address">2301 N Highland Ave, Los Angeles, CA 90068</string>
    <string name="venue_two_description">The Hollywood Bowl is known for its band shell,
        a distinctive set of concentric arches that graced the site from 1929 through 2003,
        before being replaced with a larger one beginning in the 2004 season. The shell is set
        against the backdrop of the Hollywood Hills and the famous Hollywood Sign to the northeast.</string>

    <string name="venue_three_name">Royce Hall</string>
    <string name="venue_three_address">10745 Dickson Ct, Los Angeles, CA 90095</string>
    <string name="venue_three_description">This twin-towered concert hall remains the best known UCLA landmark.
        The 1800-seat auditorium was designed for speech acoustics, but by 1982 it emerged from successive remodelings
        as a regionally important concert hall and the main performing arts facility of the university.</string>

    <string name="store_one_name">Amoeba Music</string>
    <string name="store_one_address">6400 W Sunset Blvd, Los Angeles, CA 90028 </string>
    <string name="store_one_description">This is the largest independent record store in
        the country, and it is very much alive. The variety of stock (CDs and DVDs, new
        and used) is awesome, the prices are fair and the staff know their onions.</string>

    <string name="store_two_name">Truetone Music</string>
    <string name="store_two_address">5100 Melrose Ave, Hollywood, CA 90038 </string>
    <string name="store_two_description">Nearly every inch of this Santa Monica shop is
        covered in stringed instruments and accessories. You\'ll mostly see electric
        guitars here, alongside acoustic guitars and basses—plus some slightly esoteric
        instruments, from cigar box guitars to baby sitars. In addition, the store offers
        repairs, lessons and custom pedalboards.</string>

    <string name="store_three_name">Caveman Vintage Music</string>
    <string name="store_three_address">3231 N Main St, Los Angeles, CA 90031 </string>
    <string name="store_three_description">As the name implies, the inventory here is
        largely vintage, with a particularly a handsome supply of old microphones. The shop
        also offers repairs on stringed instruments, as well as everything from tube
        amps to combo organs.</string>

    <string name="iconic_location_one_name">RockWalk</string>
    <string name="iconic_location_one_address">7425 Sunset Blvd, Los Angeles, CA 90046</string>
    <string name="iconic_location_one_description">Like a small version of courtyard at Grauman\'s
        Chinese Theatre, this little patio contains the handprints of numerous celebrities. But these
        celebrities aren\'t movie stars - they're rock musicians and guitar greats.</string>

    <string name="iconic_location_two_name">Whiskey A Go Go</string>
    <string name="iconic_location_two_address">8901 Sunset Blvd, West Hollywood, CA 90069</string>
    <string name="iconic_location_two_description">The club has been the launching pad for bands including
        Iggy And The Stooges, The Doors, No Doubt, System of a Down, Van Halen, Guns N\' Roses, and Mötley Crüe.
        In 2006, the venue was inducted into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame.</string>

    <string name="iconic_location_three_name">Hollywood Sign</string>
    <string name="iconic_location_three_address">Los Angeles, CA 90068</string>
    <string name="iconic_location_three_description">he Hollywood Sign is an American landmark and cultural
        icon located in Los Angeles, California. It is situated on Mount Lee, in the Hollywood Hills area
        of the Santa Monica Mountains. The sign overlooks Hollywood, Los Angeles.</string>




</resources>
